<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on Alexa Fredston-Hermann</title>
    <link>/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on Alexa Fredston-Hermann</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/about/</guid>
      <description>About Me I&amp;rsquo;m an ecologist using data science and synthetic approaches to solve interdisciplinary environmental problems. Ultimately, I aim to improve how humans understand, manage, and use nature. Most of my research investigates how human activities alter biogeographic patterns and ecological processes.
I&amp;rsquo;m also passionate about science communication and open science. I learned most of my R coding skills from the eco-data-science group, a data science study group that facilitates knowledge sharing within the Santa Barbara environmental community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications and CV</title>
      <link>/home/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/publications/</guid>
      <description>My publications are listed on my Google Scholar and ResearchGate pages. Feel free to contact me for PDFs of any publications. You can download my CV here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research Interests</title>
      <link>/home/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/research/</guid>
      <description>I study ecological processes and biogeographic patterns, in the context of human impacts. My work falls into three main areas:
Biogeography and Climate Change Species around the globe are shifting their ranges in response to climate change. However, many ecological and environmental processes besides climate also influence species distributions. Without understanding these other processes and how they interact with another and with climate, it’s difficult to predict range shifts and make management recommendations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/home/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>